[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ surreal music playing]
[click echoes]
[whooshing]
[explosion]
[high-pitched ringing]
[Haran] Chan, I saw a vapor trail earlier.
But that made me want
to get on a plane to go see you.
Chan.
-[EKG beeping]
-[♪ dramatic music playing]
I love you.
I love you, Chan.
[EKG beeping continuing]
[music fades]
-[dripping]
-[ventilator hisses]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ dramatic music continuing]
EPISODE 2
[doctor] The accident in the US
happened last summer, right?
It has already been three months
since you came to Korea for treatment.
Have you recalled any more memories
after our last session?
No.
I just keep
remembering one person.
I keep remembering
how she called my name and woke me.
[♪ dramatic music continuing]
But no matter how much I try to remember,
I can't recall who she is
or why I'm remembering her.
[sighs]
[doctor] Do you get images of her
in certain situations?
[Chan] No, she's always just there.
She's buried in my brain,
just like that shrapnel.
[doctor] Could it be someone you met
during that year before the accident,
back when everything's a blur for you?
[Chan sighs] I've always been alone.
There can't be anyone
who says they love me.
[grip tightens]
[sighs]
I'm not even sure if she exists,
or if it's an illusion in my head.
Or…
if I'm just crazy.
I wouldn't feel
so frustrated if I at least knew that.
[doctor] What kind of person
does she feel like to you?
[Chan] Someone I have to meet…
[♪ music intensifies]
Sir, I'll just get off here.
[lively chatter]
[♪ sentimental song playing]
[Chan] Someone who brought me back to life
and seems to hold the keys to my life.
[♪ sentimental song continuing]
[panting]
[fireworks whistle, exploding]
[song stops]
[explosion]
[people exclaiming]
[fireworks crackle]
[footstep echoes]
[♪ Baroque music playing, J.S. Bach
"Goldberg Variations, BWV 988: Aria"]
[Haran vocalizing tune]
[Haran] Try listening to it.
I saw a vapor trail earlier.
Chan.
[Haran vocalizing tune on speaker phone]
Hold on. Let me start over.
Try listening to it.
Hey, engineering student.
Chan.
Hey, Chan!
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
[panting] Hey. Sorry, Haran.
Oh, that song?
Sure. Send it to me.
I'll listen to it.
[high-pitched ringing]
[fireworks exploding]
[laptop pings]
[Hyeokchan sighs] I have to go in a hurry.
Can you message her back
and say I have to go to the lab?
Sorry. Do me a solid.
Tsk.
-[door closes]
-[sighs]
-[laptop pings]
-Tsk.
-[sighs]
-[laptop pings]
[Chan sighs]
Sorry, I'm heading to the lab.
[Haran] I was feeling trapped.
I feel like I'm surrounded by walls today.
I just messaged you
because I wanted to talk to someone.
-But you're busy. Sorry I bothered you.
-[sighs]
"Surrounded by walls"?
I FEEL LIKE I'M SURROUNDED BY WALLS TODAY
[sighs]
[Chan] If it's okay with you,
you can talk to me.
I'll be away for a few weeks.
I'm traveling around the East Coast
during vacation.
[door closes]
[Chan sighs] Hyeokchan,
you took my laptop.
My research data is in there.
[Hyeokchan]
I must've confused it with mine. Sorry.
I'll send you the data.
-Just use my laptop for now.
-[Chan sighs] I…
[sighs]
[laptop pings]
-How do I turn off that sound?
-[Hyeokchan] The messenger alarm?
Just mute it and ignore the messages
or tell her I'm at the lab.
Anyway, send me your email address.
Hey.
[echoing] Kang Hyeokchan!
[fireworks exploding]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ Baroque music playing, J.S. Bach
"Goldberg Variations, BWV 988: Aria"]
[Haran] Chan.
I love you.
I love you,
Kang Hyeokchan. [chuckles]
-[♪ dramatic music playing]
-[breathing heavily]
[footsteps echo]
[Haran] Seonu Chan… who are you?
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Oh.
Gosh, my eyes are so dry. [chuckles]
Don't get the wrong idea.
It's not like I have some big secret.
[chuckles, sniffles]
Dry eyes?
You follow me around, take photos of me,
then send them to my office.
Why are you stalking me?
-Stalking?
-I found an art museum ticket
in your shirt,
stamped with the date I went there.
I did go to the art museum,
but I wasn't following you.
-I just received a ticket.
-[sighs]
You're the one who called my name, right?
My name and my face.
You couldn't have known.
I guess you gathered a lot of info
while stalking me.
I…
I think this… will explain it.
[♪ lighthearted music playing]
I always check my partners' websites
before working with them. [chuckles]
[sighs]
You saw one photo and recognized me
from so far away? That's--
I saw you up close earlier,
looking at the Sisley painting.
Then why didn't you say so
when we met at our office?
I'm sorry if I upset you
by not telling you about it.
[sighs]
I guess… I misunderstood.
I'm sorry.
[mumbles, clears throat]
Then what are you doing at this hotel?
I'm staying here.
My company booked it for me
since it's close to Nana Atelier.
Uh… Here's my card key. [chuckles]
Room 3017.
Then why did you run away--
I wasn't running away.
I was just heading out…
Because I forgot to buy this.
It's my favorite. [chuckles softly]
I didn't even know you were in the lobby.
Yeah.
Once again, I'm sorry.
[mumbles]
[sighs in relief]
"Stalking"?
[sighs] Darn it.
Then who could have sent those photos?
[Chan] Song Haran!
[grunts]
It's the stalker!
[♪ tense music playing]
Stalker!
[Hayeong clicks tongue] You darn stalker!
Don't you dare touch my sister!
I'm reporting you!
What is he doing here?
[yelps, grunts]
[gasps, sighs] Thank you.
What?
Stalker! Stalker!
I'll get him.
[Haran exclaims]
[♪ tense music playing]
[panting]
[Haran breathes heavily]
-[Haran squeals]
-[Chan grunts]
-[Chan panting]
-[gasps]
-Are you okay?
-[gasping]
[footsteps thudding]
[Chan and stalker grunting]
[panting] Huh?
[panting]
[police siren wailing]
[keyboard clacking]
[officer bangs on table] Answer me.
What was in that bottle?
You'd better talk.
Do you want to film a vlog in prison?
Song Hayeong, be quiet.
From the smell,
it seemed like
a diluted sodium hypochlorite solution.
Ah, I mean, NaClO.
Sodium hypochlorite…
I mean, it seemed similar to chlorine.
[officer] Oh, chlorine?
I guess you majored in that field.
Why were you trying to throw that at her?
I wanted to ruin her.
She was always getting on my nerves.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Do you know each other?
[Eunchan] The design contest winner is…
-Song Haran!
-[cheering]
Thank you!
I'll treat everyone today.
[stalker] I always wondered why
you were always at the center of attention
and why everyone loved you.
It was because of Kim Nana.
You're lucky
your grandmother's a famous designer.
I quit my job
because I hated the sight of you…
[chuckles] but it's all because
of your grandma.
You made me lose everything.
Weren't you great
at pretending to be the main character
and acting like you were happy
without a concern in the world?
So why…
Why now?
-[Hayeong] Are you crazy?
-[officer] What are you doing?
[sighs]
I don't want to press charges.
Just end this here, please.
GEUMWON POLICE STATION
[Hayeong groans] She ruined her own life.
You went through so much
while you were at that company.
But why were you here? And you, Mr. Yeon?
[Hayeong] Oh... Well…
The photos really bothered me,
so I had to do something.
LOCATION TRACKER
-What are you doing?
-There's a smudge on it.
[breathing heavily]
HARAN
Something could really happen to Haran.
I didn't dig through
your phone or anything.
I just downloaded a location tracking app.
But I saw you were here
when there was no meeting.
-I got a bad feeling, so I came--
-Are you mad?
Why would you do that?
What if it really was someone dangerous?
If something happened to you…
[chuckles] Come on. I'm fine.
Bad things don't come with a warning.
People can get hurt in an instant.
"What if I'd done something differently?"
You can regret it hundreds,
thousands of times after the fact,
but it won't change a thing.
That's it!
[sighs] Hayeong,
if anything happens to you too…
Haran, look at me.
Look at me.
[breathes shakily]
I'm right here.
I'm okay.
We're all fine.
[panting]
Nothing will happen now.
It's okay.
It's all right.
You must have been startled. I'm sorry.
But why were you running
with my sister earlier?
Oh, well…
My hotel was nearby. [chuckles]
I spotted someone suspicious
following her, by coincidence.
[in English] Wow.
[in Korean] You're her savior.
Thank you so much for helping her...
Thank you. [chuckles, inhales]
Oh? [exclaims]
Your jacket got bleached.
Why did she have to throw…
I'm sorry.
I troubled you with a personal issue.
And I'm sorry about earlier too.
[stutters] It's fine.
Then I'll head back now.
-[Hayeong stutters] Bye, then.
-[Chan] Bye.
What did you mean by
"sorry about earlier"?
I grilled him, [sighs]
thinking he was the stalker.
Geez. Ungrateful much?
He even ruined his jacket
trying to help you.
[officer] Huh?
Did the other guy leave?
He probably needs treatment.
Hmm? Treatment? He just left.
Hayeong, go home first.
No, take me with you.
I can't let you go alone.
I'm really fine.
And keep this a secret, okay?
Don't report this to Grandma.
Hurry home, okay?
And keep your phone on.
[sighs, groans]
My heart…
[sighs] I thought something might happen.
Are you all right?
Gosh.
Of course. I'm fine.
I'm always fine.
Did you need something
approved by Grandma?
Let's go. It's late.
It's that way.
Come on.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
No, not that way…
Mr. Seonu.
[Chan] Oh…
[sighs] You hurt your hand earlier,
didn't you?
I'm sorry I got you mixed up in this.
Charge me for the hospital fees,
your jacket,
and any inconveniences
caused by your injury--
Are you a lawyer?
I thought you were a designer.
What?
[♪ soft pleasant music playing]
As you can see, I'm fine.
So you don't have
to draw a line like that.
I don't feel okay with it.
I hate causing trouble for others.
I'm really sorry about today.
Make sure to get your hand treated.
[Chan sighs]
Why does this keep happening?
It's scaring me.
-[leaves rustling]
-[bird chirping]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
[Yoon] She rejected me firmly.
I want to live like this.
I feel comfortable this way.
I know I'm being stupid and weird.
But…
I'm too scared.
-[door opens, closes]
-[sighs]
[door closes]
[exclaims] She's here.
Don't do this anymore, Grandma.
I'll handle things myself.
Pushing everyone away
and wasting time outside,
then hiding in a cave…
Is that how you handle things?
She…
She was with a guy.
-What?
-I was with them.
I came home early,
and she spent more time with him alone.
-Don't lie to me.
-I mean it.
Mom, Dad. You saw it, right?
I'm not lying, right?
Is it true?
I'll head upstairs first.
Tell me. Who is he?
And what's their relationship?
[♪ amusing music playing]
Uh…
Well…
-They're just talking.
-"Talking"?
Just leave her be.
Meddling will only ruin it.
Then good night.
Sleep tight.
"Talking"?
-[sighs]
-[door opens]
Gosh, Song Hayeong.
You've helped your sister again.
This household is ruined without me.
You're lucky to have such a great sister.
You made her get the wrong idea.
What? It's true that you were with a guy.
Won't it be good for her
to get the wrong idea?
Just pretend you're seeing someone.
That will save you from a lot of nagging.
No, there's no need to thank me.
[inhales sharply] I'll take this instead.
How is the animator's hand?
I gave him my business card
so he can charge me.
Business card? [sighs frustratingly]
Did I raise you like that?
If it weren't for him,
you would've gotten that chlorine…
[in English] Oh God.
[in Korean] Listen, Haran.
You should at least buy him dinner
and thank him in person…
[♪ whimsical music playing]
But of course… [smacks lips]
you're not the type to do that.
Ah. Give him some new clothes.
His jacket was ruined.
Right. Clothes.
Then next week at our meeting--
Next week?
He's here on a business trip.
He won't have many clothes.
Would that be too late?
-Then a delivery…
-Delivery?
You should at least say,
"I'm sorry, your jacket's ruined."
"I'm not sure if you'll like them,
but I got you some clothes."
Shouldn't you at least give them to him
in person and show some sincerity?
[sighs wearily] I'm tired.
I'm going to bed.
[Haran] Hayeong.
Thank you for today.
[scoffs] You were telling me
to shut up earlier.
Good night.
[Haran] Bad things don't come
with a warning.
People can get hurt in an instant.
If something happened to you…
What's this?
Why are all our shoes in the bathtub?
What do you mean? What shoes…
I'm going to wash them.
They were pretty dirty.
I have an exam in an hour.
What am I supposed to do?
What is it? Are our shoes gone?
How do I go to school today?
I have an important meeting.
You can all stay home today.
-No, I have to go.
-Don't go!
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
Just don't go. [breathing heavily]
What if something happens to you outside?
It happened to Mom and Dad.
So don't go, okay? Don't go!
Haran…
-Don't go.
-[Nana] It's okay. It's okay.
Haran, it's all right.
Just stay home.
Don't go. Don't go. Please. Please.
[♪ soft emotional music continuing]
What?
You just looked ugly. Good night.
[door closes]
[sighs, scoffs]
[sighs heavily]
Meet him in person?
[doorbell rings]
[Chan] Yes?
[inhales sharply]
What brings you here?
Someone dropped this off for you
at the front desk.
-Who?
-A young lady.
She asked me to give this to you and left.
[humming]
[inhales sharply]
How did she know my room number?
Ah. My card key.
[Haran] I'm sorry your jacket's ruined.
I'm not sure if you'll like them,
but I got you some clothes.
-[thunderclap]
-[rain pattering]
Huh?
[exclaims] No.
No.
Don't get involved.
Please, please, please don't be here.
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
[rain pattering]
[Haran] You know that particular smell
before it rains?
I love that smell.
But it disappears so quickly,
so I just stand there smelling it.
But the catch is that
you always end up with a nasty cold.
[Chan] From the smell,
it seemed like
a diluted sodium hypochlorite solution.
Ah, I mean, NaClO.
[Haran] There's another guy
who speaks like him.
[inaudible]
Ah…
You'll catch a cold.
You came here because of me, so take this.
[♪ Baroque music on earphones, J.S. Bach
"Goldberg Variations, BWV 988: Aria"]
No, it's okay.
I'm the one who's not okay.
[thunder rumbles]
Oh… [grunts]
I have another one in my room.
I'll go get it.
-Hang on.
-No, I…
[woman] Hey! Haran!
[woman gasps]
Song Haran! You're actually alive!
[exclaims] Gosh.
You suddenly cut all contact with us
and said you were going to the US.
I went to your workplace, but you quit,
and your number wasn't in service.
I was so worried about you.
I'm glad I bumped into you.
I actually booked a wedding here.
It's next spring.
-You'll be able to see everyone--
-Sorry, Yujeong.
I'm in a hurry right now. Sorry.
Huh?
Haran, wait!
Haran!
-I'll come with you to get the umbrella.
-Pardon?
Huh? Why isn't it here?
[stutters] Hang on.
Ben, my umbrella… Mmm…
Is he not here?
Oh, the concierge…
No, it's fine.
Hello?
Hello. It's Room 3017.
[clock ticking]
[♪ whimsical music playing]
It's taking a while.
I'm sure they'll come.
Right.
-[door beeps, opens]
-Oh! The umbrella…
No, it's Ben.
-Ben.
-[Ben] Oh.
Where were you?
My mother-in-law wanted
to give me some chicken stew.
Oh? Ms. Song?
Hello.
I was dropping off something
and came to borrow an umbrella.
Oh! This is great.
-You can have a meal with us…
-[shouts]
[Chan] An umbrella! [grunts]
-Here. [chuckles]
-[♪ amusing music playing]
You can take this.
-It's pouring, so get home safely.
-Right.
I'll see you at our next meeting.
Bye.
[Chan sighing]
What was that?
You become an idiot in front of Ms. Song.
Is there something going on?
Are you dating?
[sighs wearily]
There is something…
But there shouldn't be.
Ben.
Don't you feel suffocated in this hotel?
Should we just rent a house
while we're here?
Is it the hotel or your own heart
that's suffocating you?
-[Ben laughs]
-[sighs wearily, groans]
[Manjae grunting]
[grunts]
[groans, exhales heavily]
-[groaning]
-[♪ grim music playing]
[barks]
-[whining softly]
-[Manjae groaning]
[groaning]
[barking]
SHIM
Coffee House
It must be closed today.
We've been waiting,
but Mr. Park's not coming.
Thank you.
[woman] Where should we go?
Hey, Genius.
[door thuds shut]
[gasps, mumbles]
I'LL BE BACK SOON
-[man whispers] Hello?
-[gasps softly]
Isn't this Mr. Park's phone?
It is, but he's asleep right now.
[Manjae] I'll take that.
-Hello?
-[camera clicking]
-[Hadam coos, gasps]
-Give me your paw. Good boy! [squeals]
-[camera clicks]
-[giggles] Hi, I'm Genius.
-[♪ happy music playing]
Aren't I big and adorable?
Why is there a dog here?
The owner of a coffee shop
Big Sis is a regular at was hospitalized,
so she said she'd take care of him.
[groans] I wish I could keep him.
Song Hayeong, that little brat.
What? It wasn't Hayeong.
[♪ amusing music playing]
-What?
-You're here.
[Hadam sighs] Park Genius.
Isn't that such a cute name?
He was named after the coffee shop owner.
-His name's--
-Hadam. Your academy.
[gasps, groans]
Hey, Genius. I'll be back soon. See you.
See you, Grandma.
Were you close enough to someone
to look after their dog?
[chuckles nervously]
Sorry, I brought him without asking.
-[Genius slurping]
-[coos]
[Haran chuckles]
[♪ pleasant music playing]
WE MISS YOU
GET PLENTY OF REST AND FOCUS ON RECOVERING
Should I get some toys for Genius?
You're a dog, and this is a yard.
Run around all you want.
[whines]
-[doorbell rings]
-[Nana sighs]
-[Nana] Who is it?
-[man] Excuse me.
Hello.
-Is my dog Genius here?
-[Genius barks]
Hey, Genius!
-Genius!
-[Genius barks]
[exclaims] Good boy.
You must have been startled
being here without me.
-Good boy.
-Hello.
[Manjae] Ah…
My eldest granddaughter
isn't here right now.
Gosh. Where are my manners?
Thank you so much
for taking care of Genius.
It's fine. It wasn't hard
taking care of him.
But how did you…
I got discharged early.
I heard it was the house
with the coffee-colored door.
I was worried I'd come to the wrong house
for a moment. [chuckles]
I'll thank you formally next time.
-Let's go, Genius.
-Goodbye.
[Manjae] Bye.
[♪ dreamy music playing]
[Hadam] Park Genius.
Isn't that such a cute name?
He was named after the coffee shop owner.
-His name's--
-Park Manjae?
Are you Manjae, who lived in Chuncheon?
Who…
It really is you.
It's me.
The house with the persimmon tree.
Who?
PARK MANJAE
[♪ playing romantic music,
"La Vie En Rose"]
Manjae!
Nabong!
[♪ romantic music playing]
[inaudible]
The fashionista Nabong from Chuncheon?
[giggles]
Yes, it's me.
It's Nabong.
It really is you?
[both laughing]
You're really Nabong? [laughs]
Huh?
Huh? That's…
[Chan] Mr. Park, the clutter box
you're throwing away… [exclaims]
[grunts] Hello.
-[♪ soft emotional music playing]
-What are you doing here?
I'm going to live here. What about you?
You're living here? Why?
I'm close with Mr. Park.
-What brings you here?
-Why are you close?
Why?
The hotel's nearby,
so I came here every day.
And I actually received the exhibit ticket
from Mr. Park
after fixing the ice machine.
Then the regular
who fixed the ice machine…
But why stay here instead of a nice hotel?
-[Chan grunts]
-[Manjae exhales heavily]
You heard the doctor, right?
Make sure to take your meds
and get plenty of sleep.
And no overworking or drinking alcohol.
Enough with the nagging.
My ears are going to bleed.
-Gosh.
-Goodness.
There's nothing like being back home.
[sighs contentedly]
[inhales sharply]
There are a lot of rooms here.
Oh. It's a bit big for one person.
-Mmm-hmm. You must feel lonely--
-[Manjae sighs heavily]
Mr. Park, can you let me
stay in one of the rooms?
Just for three months.
[chuckles] Three months.
I was going to rent a house,
but he had some empty rooms.
And Ben is at his in-law's.
[chuckles softly]
So what brings you here?
Then the regular
who called an ambulance for him…
Hang on. Then it was you
who answered the phone?
Ah. I heard the regular I talked to
on the phone was taking care of Genius.
Yes, that regular is me.
Ah. Regular.
Regular… Mmm.
I think Mr. Park
was around here somewhere.
By the way, is he all right?
[Manjae] I'm all right.
They said
it's variant angina or something.
I just have to take medicine.
By the way, it's been so long.
You suddenly disappeared
from Chuncheon one day.
It's been over 50 years.
But I'm quite famous now.
You really didn't know?
Well, I knew the name Nana Kim,
but I never imagined
it would be you. [laughs]
Gosh, you were always
going on about la vie en rose,
and you really went to France
and achieved that dream.
[both chuckling]
But I've been running a coffee shop
in this neighborhood for over 10 years.
How is it that
we never ran into each other?
That's how the world is.
It can feel small at times
but big at others. [chuckles softly]
But how did you get so close
to my granddaughter?
She never lets anyone get close to her.
She's a regular at my coffee shop.
She stays there
almost every day until I close.
I wondered where she was staying out
so late every day.
She was there?
[♪ soft sentimental music playing]
[chuckles softly]
I guess she felt more at ease
at your coffee shop than at home with me.
I guess you did something for her
that I couldn't.
-Thanks.
-All I did was give her coffee.
I didn't do anything special.
It's been seven years,
but I never knew
she had a place to rely on.
Seven years?
That's around the time I first met her.
I think it was around summer.
I'm not sure if it's okay to ask this,
but did something happen to her
back then?
[rain pattering]
-[shop bell chimes]
-[Manjae exclaiming]
My gosh.
Hey, Genius.
It's raining cats and dogs.
It's pouring, isn't it?
It was a day when it suddenly poured.
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
But she was sitting in the rain,
crying.
[sobbing]
[Nana] Her boyfriend died back then.
He went to study in Boston,
but he suddenly died.
[♪ soft emotional music continues]
[cell phone ringing]
[box thuds]
-[grunts]
-[ringing continues]
[chuckles nervously, grunts]
[Chan exclaims]
[groans, inhales sharply]
BEN
[groans]
[stammers] You're getting a call…
Can you…
Can you hold it
on the other side? [grunts softly]
[grunts, inhales sharply]
Yes.
Hey, Ben.
[stutters] A meeting on Monday?
Okay. Bye.
Thank you. Can you put it here?
-Right. [grunts]
-[door opens]
[exclaims]
[in English] I'm back!
Genius, house!
[in Korean] Were you at our house?
You only just got discharged.
You should've called me.
It's the first time I've heard you talk
this much in seven years.
[chuckles awkwardly] Are you all right?
Yes, thanks to you.
But it's a surprise seeing
my VVIP regulars here together.
[chuckles]
Roomie, say hi. She's…
Oh. I know her.
She's a designer
at the company I'm working with.
You were working with Nabong…
I mean, the designer Nana Kim?
How do you know my grandmother's name?
It turns out she was my childhood friend.
Oh, really?
We lived in the same neighborhood
for 10 years, but I never knew.
I was so excited,
-I almost did a backflip.
-[♪ lighthearted music playing]
[laughs]
Right, I forgot.
Thank you.
You locked the doors for me
and even looked after Genius.
It's nothing.
And you can talk to me informally.
You're Grandma's friend.
Then should I start
talking to you casually?
Like a friend.
-Ah. Yes.
-[Manjae chuckles]
This is the first time
I've seen you smile like that too.
[chuckles awkwardly]
But… you must feel comfortable
on your own.
Why did you let him live here?
[clears throat]
I thought I'd feel safer
if there was someone with me.
And he's adorable.
He's a really good man.
Come sit down. I'll make you coffee.
No, it's fine. Get some rest.
Even if I don't drink coffee,
is it okay to stay here
until closing hours?
You're young.
You should be having fun outside.
You shouldn't stay cooped up
in this boring place.
This place is the most fun for me.
I can focus on work,
and I feel at ease
because it feels like nothing will happen.
Mmm.
[elevator dings]
Bring the dancheong data
I mentioned to my office.
I'll give you the files now.
[cell phone vibrating]
If it's a work call, take it.
Mr. Yeon, take the files.
-Sure.
-Here.
-Hello.
-Here, Ms. Kim.
I called about the fabric materials.
Yes, I'd like the 0.8 mm ones.
SEONU CHAN
-Ah, yes.
-[Nana] She…
-Thank you.
-[Nana] She was with a guy.
[♪ amusing music playing]
[Ben] It's an original character
that Chan created.
That character. Was it based on someone?
No, it just came to mind.
He drew his ideal type,
but he met her in real life?
Mr. Yeon, keep an eye on Ms. Song
and Seonu Chan.
Yes, ma'am.
[exclaims] That expression.
You look like a robot that's been given
an order you can't refuse.
-It's not like that.
-[♪ playful music playing]
What is it? Did Grandma…
I mean, did Ms. Kim order you
to do something again?
No, she didn't.
"No, she didn't"?
All right. Then keep working
in your robot mode.
Beep, beep, beep.
[Hayeong imitating robot beeping]
[chuckles] It's pretty fun teasing him.
[Chan] Let's take a photo.
One plus one is what?
[all] Two.
[camera clicks]
[Hayeong exclaims]
[Seung-gyu] I'm a huge animation fan.
Where did you learn art?
At CalArts.
[exclaims] CalArts? That's insane!
-Sweetie, can you draw me a caricature…
-[Hayeong and Sol laugh]
-…with your professional skills?
-Sure.
[Hayeong] Me too.
-[Seung-gyu] Me too.
-What?
-[Sol] I'll get some paper.
-When did they get so close?
Is he a capybara or what?
[Remy] Is this better, or this?
-[Seung-gyu] The second one.
-[Remy] Is this better?
How should I pose for this?
Like this?
[Chan] Hmm. [sighs]
Using a dancheong pattern
to show that she's Korean
just with her outfit…
Wow. This might be a problem.
Because it's so good. [chuckles]
Then let's develop this
with dancheong as the basic concept.
All right. I'll send this to HQ
and schedule a video call.
-I feel a bit hungry.
-[♪ whimsical music playing]
I'd like to continue our discussion
over dinner. Are you free?
Yes, I'd love that.
How about the new
Italian restaurant nearby?
It seemed really wild.
Your appetite must be wild too.
No wonder your jawline disappeared.
Have dinner without me.
What do you like?
You can eat without me. I--
You're joining.
I said we're discussing work.
[♪ elegant piano music
playing on speakers]
They look good together.
What?
I said the interior is nice.
Hello?
All right.
Sorry, I have to go.
Something urgent came up.
Then let's--
Sit. I didn't mean you were going.
I'm sorry. Enjoy your dinner.
See you at the meeting,
Animator Seonu Chan.
Right. I'll see you at the meeting.
[inhales sharply]
If you feel uncomfortable, we can just…
Here are the menus.
I'm sorry, but we'll just…
[Hayeong] You should at least buy him
dinner and thank him in person…
Let's just eat.
I'll buy.
What?
Ah. Okay…
Can you recommend something?
-Take your time. Just look here.
-Ah.
Our rollatini is our signature dish,
made with sliced eggplants…
-She doesn't like eggplants.
-How did you know I don't like eggplants?
What? Oh…
Many people dislike eggplants.
Right?
-[waiter] Right…
-Me too.
I dislike them as well.
Can you just give me
something you can prepare quickly?
-Me too.
-All right.
[sighs contentedly]
-The interior really is nice.
-[cell phone buzzes]
[Chan sighs]
[Nana] Repetition means
your heart has already stirred.
Instead of writing his name over and over,
follow your heart.
"Name"?
[Nana] Mr. Yeon, take the files.
[sighs, mumbles]
Let me apologize first.
SEONU CHAN
Oh? Why is my name there?
Well…
I wrote this when I thought
you were my stalker,
but I think Ms. Kim saw this
and thought I had feelings for you.
That's probably why
we ended up having dinner alone.
Ah…
[sighs]
I'll explain this to her…
[Hayeong] Just pretend
you're seeing someone.
That will save you from a lot of nagging.
I should tell her…
But is it okay if I don't?
Pardon?
It's a bit complicated,
but I think
this will be a good opportunity
to put my grandmother's mind at ease.
Oh. Sure.
If it helps you, then it's fine with me.
Thank you. I'll make sure
this won't cause you any trouble.
All right.
[speaker squeaks]
[grunts]
[high-pitched ringing]
There must have been
an issue with the connection. I'm sorry.
It's fine.
[♪ elegant classical music
playing on speakers]
[Nana] How did the two seem?
[Taeseok] I'm not sure yet.
REPRESENTATIVE
KIM NANA
I set things up for them,
so we'll know soon.
-You can go now.
-I'll take you home.
I'm not a child. I can go home by myself.
You don't look well these days.
And you haven't gotten
any checkups for years.
At least take these. They're vitamins.
You're not my chauffeur
or secretary anymore.
If you've become the COO,
you should stop doing such things.
Why would a COO take care
of my granddaughters as well?
I'm doing it because I want to.
Then don't work too late.
[door closes]
[sighs]
I wonder what they're up to now.
[♪ elegant classical music continuing]
Sorry, I shouldn't have asked
what I did earlier.
I'll take that back…
-[groans softly, inhales sharply]
-[cutlery scraping]
-Are you not feeling well?
-What?
-[grunts]
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[whooshes]
-[grunts softly]
-[ice cubes crunch]
-[clattering]
-[grunts softly]
-[clinking]
[♪ tense music playing]
-[glasses clink]
-[corks pop]
[groans softly]
Excuse me…
-[server 1 yelps]
-[shatters]
[gasps]
[server 1 exclaims]
I'm so sorry. I'll pay for all this.
Can you put in the order again?
Just a moment, please.
All right.
[server 2] I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[♪ tense music continues]
-[breathing heavily]
-[door opens, closes]
Are you okay? Do you feel dizzy?
[sighs] Is there a pharmacy nearby?
I'm sorry.
I don't do well in noisy places.
-Is it hard being around crowds?
-No.
Mmm…
[high-pitched ringing]
[inhales deeply]
-I can't hear… on this side.
-[♪ soft emotional music playing]
I'm usually fine,
but the sounds get mixed up
when it's noisy inside.
And I can't even hear
the person right in front of me.
It's hard to tell
the direction of the sounds.
Excuse me.
Excuse me! No, not that way…
Can you hold it on the other side?
[♪ soft emotional music continuing]
But I'm a skilled artist, I'm friendly,
and with my looks… [chuckles]
What?
I'm a really lucky guy besides the fact
that I can't hear on one side,
so you don't have to look at me like that.
[Chan inhales sharply]
[sighs] I'll go deal
with the mess I caused in there.
No, it's noisy in there.
I'll go bring our stuff.
[door opens, closes]
[inhales sharply]
I…
Hang on.
Excuse me for a moment.
[♪ tender song playing]
I'm just taking care
of your ruined clothes, as a designer.
It's not because I feel bad or anything.
-Why are you drawing a line like that?
-Think however you want.
Thank you.
Thanks
for caring.
I took care of it for now.
There.
No, you'll catch a cold…
It was just to style my outfit.
I'll tell my grandmother
she had a misunderstanding.
It's a good opportunity.
It's fine with me--
I'm not fine with it.
I don't like feeling indebted.
Anyway, I'll bring our stuff.
[Chan] How did you get close to Ms. Song?
[Manjae] What? Well… [chuckles]
I think we're close,
but I'm not sure about her.
But why do you ask?
Well…
It feels like she always draws a line
and doesn't let me cross it.
She didn't use to…
It just feels like it's hard
to get close to her. [chuckles]
I've seen her every day
for the past seven years,
but I had no idea what she did
or where she lived.
She never talks about herself.
-[♪ soft pleasant music playing]
-She was always drawing clothes,
so I just assumed she was a designer.
She always came by herself
and stayed here quietly.
-[rain pattering]
-[Manjae exclaims]
[Chan] Did she ever come with anyone else?
[Manjae] No, never.
Not once in seven years.
She was always by herself.
Always.
[Haran sneezing]
[sighs]
Did you catch a cold?
No, I was just sneezing.
[sneezes]
[Haran sighs]
[sighs softly]
-Huh? Where did it go?
-[♪ mysterious music playing]
Gosh, you're stirring up dust.
What are you doing?
I can't find my drawing pen.
Where did it go?
Where are you going?
It's time for our meeting.
[sighs]
[in English] I really liked
the, uh... the dancheong idea.
So could you tell me
a little bit more about it?
Of course.
Director Song will go over it for you.
Director Song?
[Hayeong coughing, speaking Korean]
The data overview.
Oh, the data…
[in English] Dancheong is
a traditional Korean coloring technique.
[in Korean] Thank you.
[Nana in English]
Commonly found in palaces and temples.
It involves painting
wooden architecture with…
Okay, so I'll see you at the next meeting.
We'll talk more about it then.
All right. Bye-bye, everybody.
[all] Bye!
[Ben] See you.
[Remy sighs, speaking Korean]
Great work, everyone.
[clears throat]
What kind of attitude was that?
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
[sighs]
[♪ pensive music playing]
[gasping]
Gosh. It's not here!
Hang on. Where did I last use it?
Right. The restaurant!
[breathing heavily]
The restaurant?
NAUM LOST-AND-FOUND LIST
We haven't found anything like that.
Could I search for it myself?
There are customers eating inside.
But if you dropped it,
we would have found it while cleaning.
[sighs]
I'm really sorry,
but can I take a look after you're closed?
Just for 30, no, 10 minutes.
It's really valuable to me,
so I have to find it.
Please.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
[Chan] No.
You're going downtown later anyway.
Just get me something I can gift.
Anything that a woman
in her twenties can use.
We're not close enough
to ask for favors like that.
Do that for me, okay?
-[door opens, closes]
-[sighs heavily]
[shopkeeper in English] Is it a gift?
I could engrave it if you'd like.
[sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
[Chan sighs]
Did you find it?
I'll look for it after they close.
I'm sure it'll be there.
Let's go. We can stay at SHIM
and come back to look for it.
No, this is a personal matter.
I can find it by myself.
[coughs, sniffles]
-Wear this for now.
-No…
I'm just trying to help
with your coughing, as an animator.
Plus, even if you dropped it here,
someone could have taken it.
Anyway, let's go somewhere warm--
I'll…
deal with this by myself.
Thanks for your concern,
but leaving is helping me.
[coughs, sniffles]
What are you going to do, then?
Wait out here
when you're coughing like this?
It's just some pen.
[scoffs]
You don't know anything about it.
I'm already upset
without you making it worse, so just…
[sighing]
[stutters] Where are you going?
You won't leave me alone, so I'm leaving.
It might be "just some pen,"
but I have to find it, no matter what.
[grunts]
Fine, I'll leave.
-So wear this.
-Please, just…
[Chan clears throat]
Just take it.
[♪ sentimental music continuing]
[Haran sighs]
"Just some pen."
[sighs]
I feel bad for saying that.
Hey, roomie.
-Yes.
-I'm sorry.
Gosh. Sorry. [chuckles]
Oh, my…
You must have gone through
something awful.
-You always seemed so cheerful.
-Oh…
[inhales sharply]
Do you want to try touching it?
[chuckles] It doesn't hurt at all now.
[scoffs]
It seems you got something drawn
on your chest.
[Chan] Ah. My tattoo?
But why is it "memento mori"
of all phrases?
It's like a warning to myself.
-A warning?
-Yes.
"You never know when you might die."
"So live your life without regrets."
Something like that. [chuckles]
[inhales sharply]
But what's that for?
Didn't you just pick this up somewhere?
Yes, it was snapped.
[chuckles]
Well, it grew roots.
What?
[exclaims, chuckles]
I thought it would wither soon. [exclaims]
I think it's time
to take it out of the glass.
If I move it into a pot
and take good care of it, it'll grow well.
[Manjae chuckles]
Here you go.
"Time to take it out"?
By the way, roomie.
-Yes?
-So, are you living without any regrets?
[♪ sentimental song playing]
Why would you do that?
If something happened to you…
[Yujeong] Gosh.
You suddenly cut all contact with us.
Sorry, Yujeong. I'm in a hurry right now.
It's really valuable to me,
so I have to find it.
It might be "just some pen,"
but I have to find it.
[Manjae] I think it's time
to take it out of the glass.
[♪ sentimental song continuing]
[sighs]
[door opens]
[♪ sentimental song continues]
-[cell phone beeps, dialing]
-[Haran] Chan, do you remember
how I said I felt like
I was surrounded by walls?
[vibrating]
I suddenly found myself
unable to sketch anything,
and I had no energy.
I just wanted to give up on everything.
[Chan panting]
[Haran] But when I first held the pen
you gave to me for my birthday,
I was suddenly able to draw something.
And I won first place
in the contest with it.
I would have run away
if I hadn't gotten such great results.
Excuse me.
[Haran] So you saved me.
Thanks to you and this pen,
I realized how much I love my job.
It's a really precious pen to me.
-"Haran" is engraved on the lid.
-Thank you.
I'll draw lots of amazing clothes
and become a great designer.
-[staff] Excuse me.
-[sighs]
I'm sorry, but we have to go home now.
[sighs] Right. I'm sorry.
If you ever find it,
can you contact me through this number?
[Manjae] So, are you living
without any regrets?
[Chan] No.
I think I'll have a lot of regrets later.
[Manjae] Then what should you do
to not have regrets?
[Chan] I want someone
to have joy in their life.
Instead of their bleak life now,
I want it to be vibrant, like before.
I lived like that thanks to her.
[Manjae] Then you can give her that joy.
[Chan] I'd love to,
but I'm not sure if I have the right.
[Manjae] I don't think you need rights
to want someone to be happy,
as long as you're sincere about it.
[cell phone vibrating]
-Hello? Did you find--
-[Chan] You're still there, right?
Are you there?
I have something to tell you.
No, I'm…
[Chan panting]
I guess you haven't found it yet.
Well…
I'm sorry. I was rude earlier.
Hang on…
[panting]
[exclaims]
"Let's live so I won't have any regrets
when they close my coffin."
That's my life motto.
But I thought I'd have regrets.
That's why I came here.
I didn't want that to happen.
I return to the US in three months,
and I probably won't come back to Korea.
Why are you telling me this?
I want to meddle in each other's affairs,
feel indebted,
and have fun together with you, Ms. Song.
What are you saying?
Let's not think about the past or future.
Let's just have fun
until I head back.
Just until next spring.
Let's have fun like we're on a picnic.
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
[Manjae] But I'm really curious.
Who is this person you want to be happy?
[laptop pings]
-[sighs]
-[laptop pings]
[pinging continues]
[pinging rapidly]
[groaning]
-I was trying to die…
-[groans]
[EKG beeping]
And I almost died.
But she brought me back twice.
A grateful disruption
that made me live again.
Is it okay if I start being
really nice to you from now on?
[♪ upbeat love song playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
[Haran] I don't think
we'll ever be friends.
[Nana] Someone who's "talking" to a guy
is home at this hour?
[Haran] I can't even go to the cafe
I love the most because of you!
I don't need any new variables.
[Manjae] A lot of them
just wither and die.
[Chan] I'll move out
so we don't have to see each other again.
I'll be gone
once our contract is over in three months.
[Haran sighs]
[Haran] I'd like to step away
from this collaboration project.
[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park